Guide to the Reston Board of Commerce records, 1985-1996
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Reston Board of Commerce records
1985-1996
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Calvin Hackeman
C0136
6.25 linear feet (13 boxes)
The Reston Board of Commerce records is a collection of papers from Calvin Hackeman's service as the Reston Board of Commerce President. The majority of the collection is correspondence to and from Calvin Hackeman. Included in the collection as well are reports, plans, and proposals presented to the board. Also there are different types of publications such as brochures, flyers, booklets and articles.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the Reston Historic Trust on December 16, 2008.
Historical Information
Reston is a planned community in Northern Virginia. Robert E. Simon, Jr., the founder of Reston, purchased the land with the proceeds from the sale of Carnegie Hall in New York City in 1961. Construction began in 1963 with the building of Lake Anne. The Reston Board of Commerce was organized in 1982. The goal of the organization is to help to promote the growth and development of business in the Reston area. The board was renamed Greater Reston Chamber of Commerce in 1993.
Scope and Content
The Reston Board of Commerce records is a collection of papers from Calvin Hackeman's service as the Reston Board of Commerce President. The majority of the collection is correspondence to and from Calvin Hackeman. Included in the collection as well are reports, plans, and proposals presented to the board. Also there are different types of publications such as brochures, flyers, booklets and articles.
Series one is titled correspondence. The series contains mostly correspondence to and from Calvin Hackeman pertaining to Reston Board of Commerce business. There are also other people such as Karl Ingebritsen and Karen Connell among the correspondents.
Series two is titled meetings. The series contains information from meetings of the Board of Commerce. Some of the information are meetings minutes, meeting agendas and various other documents.
Series three is titled reports. The series contains different reports, proposals and plans for the Reston Board of Commerce. The information included in the series includes by-laws, marketing plans, research and various other topics.
Series four is titled finance. The information in this series pertains to the financial side of the Reston Board of Commerce. Included in the series are budget, statements and other financial documents.
Series five is titled publications. The series contains brochures, booklets, flyers and various other publications. Most of the publications contain information relating to different programs in Reston such as the annual expo.
Series six is titled general information. The information in this series covers a variety of topics about the Reston Board of Commerce. Included in the series are planners from Calvin Hackeman, membership lists, notes, newsclippings and other information.
Arrangement
Organized into six series.
Series 1: Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Boxes 1-4)
Series 2: Meetings, 1990-1991 (Boxes 4-5)
Series 3: Reports, 1988-1992 (Boxes 5-6)
Series 4: Finance, 1997-1992 (Boxes 6-7)
Series 5: Publications, 1989-1992 (Boxes 7-9)
Series 6: General Information, 1985-1996 (Boxes 9-13)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
The Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia, and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Persons:
Hackeman, Calvin.
Corporate Names:
Greater Reston Chamber of Commerce.
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Housing--Virginia--Reston.; Planned communities--Virginia--Reston.
Contents List
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1988-1992; (3.5 boxes)
  The series contains mostly correspondence to and from Calvin Hackeman pertaining to Reston Board of Commerce business. There are also other people such as Karl Ingebritsen and Karen Connell among the correspondents.
  - Congress, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Coverletters, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Meeting Reminder), April 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Meeting Reminder), April 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman, September 24, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Fax), November 9, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman, May 21, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Thank You), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Form Letter), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Thank You), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Form Letter), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Cover Letter), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman (Form Letter), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - From: Calvin Hackeman, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - From: David Ross, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - From: Karl J. Ingebritsen, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - From: Linda Mallison, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - From: McGuire Woods Battle and Boothe, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - From: Richard Lager (Form Letter to Senators), September 24, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - From: Various Corporations, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - House of Representatives, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mail, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Remarks, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Senate, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The McCandless Company, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - To: Calvin Hackeman, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - To: Calvin Hackeman, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - To: Calvin Hackeman (Fax), November 26, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - To: Calvin Hackeman, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - To: Calvin Hackeman, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - To: Executive Committee Members, April 19, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - To and From: Audrey Moore, 1989 and 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - To and From: Karen Connell, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - To and From: Karen Connell, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - To and From: Karl J. Ingebritsen, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - To: Martha Pennino, 1989 and 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - To: Reston Board of Commerce (RBC) (Committee), 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - To: Reston Board of Commerce (RBC) Officers and Directors, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - To: Reston Board of Commerce (RBC) Members, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Series 2: Meetings, 1990-1991; (1 box)
  The series contains information from meetings of the Board of Commerce. Some of the information are meetings minutes, meeting agendas and various other documents.
  - Agendas, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Committee Stationary, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - List of Officers, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Organizational Charts, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Priorities, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Series 3: Reports, 1988-1992; (1 box)
  The series contains different reports, proposals and plans for the Reston Board of Commerce. The information included in the series includes by-laws, marketing plans, research and various other topics.
  - Action Plans, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - By-Laws, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Development corridor Consortium, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Goals, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Governance Options, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Human Services Today, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Jobs To Do, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Marketing/Communications, 1988 and 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Marketing/Public Relation Plans, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Skills, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Member Preference Survey Results, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Plans, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Personnel Manual, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Plan of Year, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Planning Determination, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - President's Messages, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Project Proposals, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Public/Private Partnership, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Regional Transportation Authority for Washington, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Report of the Advisory Committee On the Future of the US Space Program, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Research and Development, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Reston Board of Commerce (RBC) Resolutions, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Reston Partnership, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Small Business Committee, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Space Is Our Future, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Staff Report, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - The Open Partnership, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Series 4: Finance, 1987-1992; (1 box)
  The information in this series pertains to the financial side of the Reston Board of Commerce. Included in the series are budget, statements and other financial documents.
  - A Study of Financial Resources, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Advisory to the Media, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Budget Comparison, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Compiled Financial STatements, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Costs, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Dulles Corridor, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fiscal Condition, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - McLean Hilton Statement, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Members Dues, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Monthly Statement, November 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Statements, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Statements, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Notes, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Office of the Governor, November 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Statements, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Series 5: Publications, 1989-1992; (2 boxes)
  The series contains brochures, booklets, flyers and various other publications. Most of the publications pertain information relating to different programs in Reston such as the annual expo.
  - Breakfast Seminars, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Brochures, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Brochures, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Brochures, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Business Report, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Commission of the Bicentennial of the US Constitution, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Discovereston, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Expo '89 Booklets, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Expo, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Expo '92 Booklets, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - First Bank Express, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Flyers, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Governing Documents of the Reston Association (User's Guide), 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Innovations, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Interfaith, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Introduction To Type, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Leadership Communique Flyers, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lifeline, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Network Night, 1988 and 1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - News From Reston Town Center, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Monthly Events, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Monthly Events, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Newsline, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Newsline, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Newsline, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Newsline, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Paceletter, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pathways, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Reston Board of Commerce (RBC) Luncheon, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Reston Board of Commerce (RBC) Newsletter, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Reston Booklets, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Reston Community Center: Center Stage, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Reston Directory, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Reston: Realtor Alert, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Seneca Falls Greenhouses and Nurseries, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Series 6: General Information, 1985-1996; (4.5 boxes)
  The information in this series covers a variety of topics about the Reston Board of Commerce. Included in the series are planners from Calvin Hackeman, membership lists, notes, newsclippings and other information.
  - A Night on the Town, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Agreement, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Appraisal, April 11, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Article, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Association for Commuter Transportation, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Atlantic Talent Agency, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Award Banquet, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Benevolence Award Application, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Blank Forms, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - "Bonds", 1990s (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - "Bone Marrow Transplants", April 1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Business Directory Advertisements, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Business Personal Property, September 1, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Calvin Hackeman's Completed Survey, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Candidates' Night, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Cards and Award, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Coalition for Space Station Continuity, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Congressional REcords, June 6, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Copy of the US Constitution, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Corporate Members, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Corporations List, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Contracts, January 13, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Effective Leadership, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Expo, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Expo Booth, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Exposition '88, September 29, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Fact Sheets, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Fairfax Taxes", 1990s (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Fax Copies, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Governance Survey, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Group Rosters, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - HCA Reston Hospital Center, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hospital Center, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - House Joint Resolution, February 1, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - House Joint REsolution, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Human Service Survey, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Invitations, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Leadership Communique, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "Jo-Hungry Texans...", March 12, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Alert, August 18, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Mardi Gras, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Marketing Strategies, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Mascoma Valley Messenger", November 8, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Membership Applications, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Membership Drive, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Membership Information, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Membership Listing, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Member Plate, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Mini Pages, January 20, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Music List, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - NASA Articles, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - National Conference of Bicentennial Leaders, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - New Releases, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - "New Skyline Envisioned for Northern Virginia", March 11, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Newsclippings, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Newsclippings (copies), 1990s (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Note Cards, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Notes, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Notes, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Slogan, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Officers and Board of Directors List, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Overhead Slides, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Potential Donors, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Potential Topics, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - President's Remarks, January 10, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Public Hearing, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Questions and Answers, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Questions and Answers for Debate, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Reston Board of Directory (RBC) Directory, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Reston Community Center Brochure, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Reston Street Map, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Reston Quiz, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Retreat, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Review Committee Conclusions, April 9, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Rules, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Rules Relating to Motions, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Small Business STrategies, October 1991 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Space Station Freedom Hot Line, April 15, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Survey, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Tax District, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - "Tech Index", February 21, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Tenth Annual Jennings Randolph Forum, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Telemarketing Techniques, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Testimony, April 10, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - The Capitol Report, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - The Connection, May 16, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Hit List, 1990s (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The List, 1990s (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Transportation Comments, 1990s (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Transportation Management Associations", December 2, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Transportation Planning...", 1990s (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Tysons/Dulles Corridor, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - "US Transit Financing", November 27, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "Washington Bypass Study", 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - "Wasted Health Care Dollars", July 1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Welcome From Cal Hackeman, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Who Speaks For Growth Centers?", November 1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Six Year Planner, January 1984-August 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, July 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, August 1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, June 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, May 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, April 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, March 1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, February 1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, January 1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, November 1985 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, October 1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, September 1985 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, August 1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, December 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Six Year Planner, January 1987-August 1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Six Year Planner, January 1988-August 1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, July 1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, August 1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, September 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, October 1988 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, November 1988 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, December 1988 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, January 1989 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, February 1989 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, March 1989 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, April 1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Six Year Planner, January 1989-August 1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Hand Book For Your 5 In 1 Pocket Day-Timer, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, June 1989 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, May 1989 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, July 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, August 1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, September 1989 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, October 1989 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, November 1989 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, December 1989 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, January 1990 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, February 1990 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, March 1990 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, April 1990 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, May 1990 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, February 1991 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, March 1991 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, April 1991 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, May 1991 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, June 1991 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, July 1990 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, September 1990 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, October 1990 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, December 1990 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Six Year Planner, January 1990-August 1991 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Handbook For Your Wire-Bound 5 In 1 Pocket Day-Timer, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, June 1990 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, August 1990 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Pocket Day-Timer, January 1991 (Box 13, Folder 55)